

- Gothenburg, Sweden
- +46 79 102 72 10
- tbelbek.com
- in linkedin.com/in/tbelbek

## Summary

Experienced in C# for 9 years (from web forms to .net 6), C++ for 2 years, Python for 1 Year,

Ex-Project Technical PO for 2 years, leading up to 25 people and collaborating with other teams in an AGILE environment.

5+ years of experience in AGILE, Registered SCRUM master in Scrum inc. for 2 years,

Instructor for juniors and mentees from every level,

Presenter in company wide live events, tech or non tech-based,

Ex-Athlete, amateur sportsman.

## Work experience

## **Software Factory Engineer**

04-05-2022 - Present

#### Volvo Cars Company

#### **KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:**

Automating the embedded product software cycle including QA and gating.

- · Product gating and quality management
- · Including setting up pipelines from scratch
- · Highly communicating with the teams in software factory
- Documenting and change management
- · Mentoring other team members in software development

KEY TECHNOLOGIES USED: Python, Cynosure, Linux

#### **Senior Software Developer**

07-03-2022 - Present

doWhile Consulting Scandinavia AB

#### **KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:**

In-house product development

KEY TECHNOLOGIES USED: .NET 5, .NET 6, C#, MVC, GitLab

## **Software Development Technology Manager**

01-07-2021 - 25-02-2022

#### KoçSistem

#### **KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:**

- · Digital product management
- Development tasks (around 50%)
- Leading team (up to 25 people)
- High level road mapping
- Process/Agile management
- DevOps management
- Product Owner of HR employee experience project
- · Mentoring and leading employees to develop career in software development
- Performing presenter/moderator tasks on company's live events

KEY TECHNOLOGIES USED: .NET Core, C#, MVC, Git, Azure

**KEY ACHIEVEMENTS**: Completing the first year of the roadmap I created how to convert existing technology and infrastructure to a modern version, including devops, security, project architecture and also agile maturity.

As a Technology Manager;

- 4 Key Metrics implementation in DevSecOps completed %75
- 0 Pentest results in web applications
- 2x Product Release Rate
- · Test frameworks implementation
- Database automation implementation
- AGILE maturity increased from 3,1/4 to 3,7/4

#### KoçSistem

#### **KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:**

- · Responsible for team's planning, performance, technical leading
- Architectural support to projects
- Frontier on DevOps transformation, code quality measure metrics implementation, Agile transformation, integration management, app ecosystem management.

KEY TECHNOLOGIES USED: .NET Core, C#, MVC, Git, Azure

**KEY ACHIEVEMENTS**: Creating road map how to convert existing technology and infrastructure to a modern version, including devops, security, project architecture and also agile maturity.

As a team lead;

- · Git transformation, branch, PR and Code Review strategies implemented
- %60 decreased SLA rate
- DevOps implementation of all applications on Azure
- %55 decrease in bugs in new features released
- User satisfaction increased %50 percent

#### **Senior Software Developer**

13-03-2018 - 29-02-2020

#### KoçSistem

#### **KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:**

- Developing warehouse management system using GPS location system including:
  - o Card access administration
  - o Factory production band audit and management
  - Truck tracing
- Providing leading support about software architecture and solution development in the team.
- Consultant to KocSistem Business Partners in Turkey and around the world like Arcelik, Beko, Bosch Siemens Hausgerate, Aygaz.

**KEY TECHNOLOGIES USED**: Visual Basic, .net Core 3.0, C#, various ORM tools (Dapper, EF), Redis, Elastic Search, RabbitMQ, MVC, Git, Azure, GPS location system

**KEY ACHIEVEMENTS**: Some of the developed modules were added as a contribution to company-wide in the project framework of KocSistem. One project received an award in 2019 IDC Awards and a Customer Satisfaction Award in Turkey.

- · Contribution to company wide framework
- 2 Award in one project

# Senior Software Developer

12-12-2016 - 12-03-2018

#### **Antasya Software & Consultancy**

### **KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:**

- Developing public transport solutions in C# and C++
- Working with IETT (Istanbul public transport agency) and Modyo (The company who is running the in-car and in-train advertisement signage solution)
- Performing research about the "Green stop project" which is about E-lnk screens and solar power with embedded pcs in stops to provide info and also media content to customers(In this case, passengers.)
- Worked at the final edge of the new version of digital signage solution of "Modyo" company.
- Developing Web UI with MVC framework and devices with Android 4.4

KEY TECHONOLOGIES USED: C++, .NET, C#, MVC, Git, Jenkins, Azure

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS: Created a new AVL solution for IETT and Malatya Municipality

### Software Consultant

27-08-2014 - 12-12-2016

### BilgeAdam Corporate Consultancy Company

#### **KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:**

- Consultancy an Technical support for top 500 companies like Borusan, Koçsistem, Kordsa, Medical part etc int 10+ projects.
- Projects developed were in diverse areas: Stock Management, Public activity planning, In house resource and talent
  management, Health services management with patient services

KEY TECHNOLOGIES USED: .NET C#, MVC C#, JavaScript

**Education** 

#### **Management of IT Systems**

Beykent University, Istanbul

Master's Degree, Science

**Physics** 2008 - 2014

Marmara University, Istanbul

Bachelor's Degree, Science

## Technical skills and competencies, Experience in years

C# 9 years .Net Core 5 years C++ 2 years JavaScript 8 years Java 1 year Python 1 year MVC 9 years HTML5 8 years **Restful Services** 9 years Microservices 1 year Dapper 2 years React.js 1 year Qt Framework 2 years PL/SOL 3 years **Embedded Systems** 3 years Google Maps API 2 years Azure DevOps 5 years CI/CD 5 years **Jenkins** 1 year Agile 8 years Scrum 8 years Waterfall 8 years Web Development 9 years Linux 4 years

## **Professional Training and Acquired Certificates**

Registered Scrum Master, Scrum Inc, Nov 2021

**Agile Leadership**, Coursera, Sept 2021 (a set of 5 certificates: Agile Leadership: Introduction to Change; Developing an Agile Team; Agile Organization; Agile Leadership; Agile Leadership Capstone)

Introduction to Software Product Management, Coursera, Sept 2021

Communication Strategies for a Virtual Age, Aug 2021

Leadership in 21 rst Century, Coursera, Aug 2021

How to Manage a Remote Team, Coursera, Jul 2021

Mentorship Skills Workshop, Qmark Consultancy, June 2021

Shaping up with Angular, Code School, Aug 2015

MS: Programming in C#, Microsoft, Jul 2015

MCPS: Microsoft Certified Professional, Microsoft, Apr 2015

2016 - 2018

MS: Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3, Microsoft Apr 2015

| Languages ———————————————————————————————————— |                                  |
|--|----------------------------------|
| Turkish  | Native/C2                        |
| English  | Full professional proficiency/C1 |

Created with **TVisualCV**